Yajubu!
Ya-juju!
Ready!
Start!
Bring it all in
The dance of instinct, the authenticity of proof
That's how we prove our existence
Studio #1
It's a tanuki, it's a tanuki, right? I'm getting a new-new feeling.
Well then, I will end the question.
Captain 1, please take care of it.
Please give me your best regards.
Thank you very much.
Wow, for the first time, I'm not nervous about a live birth.
I'm looking forward to it.
I will do my best to make it a good memory.
Today is my biometric event, so...
I'm sorry. I heard that because I'm a bit brusque.
That's okay. Fine, but I'm going to do my best to make sure I grow.
I don't know. It's like, you're on stage...
You're so low.
I'm losing my costume.
Is that so?
You're looking a little rustic today.
Your hair could be a little more sparkly.
It's fine, but... I just need to make it look a little more shiny.
Nice to meet you all.
Nice to meet you.
This is me.
Please stop.
I love you.
Seino
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday dear Summer
Happy Christmas
Happy birthday to you
I'm not satisfied with an unfinished future
If I come pouring stars to you
I wanted to do something different this year.
I thought I'd sing with each member.
I've prepared a chaise coaster!
Beyond the night, distant memories
You point your finger
With a sad voice
Farewell
I want you to continue with your scars
I wish
Even though I can't take your hand
I can't hold your hand, but I can hold you in my arms
In this raven, if I shine my tears
I'm right with you, even if it's only vague.
What do you want to do? A dream so long it waits for the night
A new neon light.
From the queen you hate so much.
Fall in love with me.
Thank you!
Play with the voice of ayaka-saka
The day has come Swimming in the sky
We searched for each other, Celery
Celery
Serve from the screen
Yes, I'm going to YouTube!
Congratulations.
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
It was fun.
To be continued?
Continue in two parts. I'll do my best.
I'll do my best
I love it, don't you?
Nan, I think by the time you see this, the day will be over.
You really did a great job.
Thanks for all your hard work.
I think Mi-chan's hair looks so cute with the M
Oh no!
I think it's cute.
There's a V in it
Please drop the name all the way down
I...
No, I don't want to.
No, no, no.
Not when it's good.
It's time for the second part.
I'm a little nervous.
I'll do my best. I'll be as close as Lyrica.
Thanks for your help.
What's with no rings?
The one you did at the beginning.
What?
Thanks for the help.
What? You're fixing me up?
Just in case.
You're cute.
Oh, really?
You're right.
No, you're not right.
It's cute.
Correct?
I got three guesses.
That's a very simple thought.
It's a great thought.
Good job, guys.
Buy some apples.
Congratulations.
Good work.
Simple woman.
This is amazing, isn't it?
I told her she'd look cute in it.
I see. She was a cute girl.
Ah, ouch.
But it was fun.
Congratulations.
It was fun. Thank you so much. You will be a good adult.
Good luck.
I didn't say it, but I'm blurting out something.
Really, as expected, no.
Moo-chan, don't shoot.
Good morning.
What day is it today?
That's right. It's a music video shoot.
Banser, you are getting along well with each other today.
You may be surprised to hear that we are really getting along so well.
I'm going to do my best today, too. I'm going to do my best.
Good morning.
May I come in?
It looks like none of the members are available right now, so I'll leave it at that.
Thank you very much.
What's with the sky and the fish? Isn't that the best quality you've ever had?
Time settlement.
Yes. Time settlement.
I was just talking with the manager about the possibility of the director appearing on YouTube.
Have you ever shown your face?
I don't think so.
But his voice makes me think, "Ah! I'm like, "Ah!
The cat's.
You have the same face as your voice.
Really? She has the same face as the voice?
You can tell.
I think it's exactly the face you're imagining. It's going to be very soothing.
If you get a chance.
I'm sure she'll make an appearance when she gets a chance, so please look forward to it.
Yay!
I'm looking forward to it.
Today, we have a music video for "Sky and Fish.Today, we have a music video for Sky and Fish.
The theme is that it is the rainy season and the weather is too bad to go outside.
It's a peaceful time to spend in the rainy season.
I will draw a picture with a VHS taste.
I'm going to draw a VHS style picture.
You can look at the camera if you want.
Yes, turn on the camera.
Turn on the switch.
Yes, camera.
Yes, switch.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, my God, it's swollen.
It's swollen.
It's swollen, it's swollen, it's swollen.
By the looks of it.
Music video shooting has begun!
It's the sky and the fish.
We won't be cutting outside today, but...
But we're going to fight!
We'll do our best!
Oh!
Yeah!
Are you sure?
Yeah, I think so.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
I love it!
You don't mind if I go on YouTube?
I'm gonna get Mosaic.
I'm getting Mosaic.
Oh, okay.
Uh, before this.
Can I take my macarons off?
Let's do this face.
I'm not gonna touch this one.
Okay. - Okay.
Like this.
You're not expressing your big line like that?
Oh, it's coming out a little bit.
Oh, it's coming out a little bit?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
He's the best with this face.
Your eyebrows are so high.
And you have to do it a little bit more often.
Oh, yeah.
Yes, yes, yes.
Isn't it natural?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
No, no, no.
It's a big mouth.
Yes, it is.
So, are we all good?
Yes, ma'am.
All right, then.
Have it your way.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
On the contrary.
The expression on your face...
Isn't she...
Isn't he cute?
His mouth was open.
A little.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
You have a pretty face.
That's pretty close to the size of my mouth.
Oh, bye.
Got any tea?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Uh...
Lemon tea?
Oh, please.
That's how big my glass is.
May I? This one.
It's fine.
No, it's not.
No, it's fine.
Yes, it's okay.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Hey.
Okay, let's start from the other side.
From the other side.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Let's see everyone from here.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Sit down.
Can I make a pretty face?
I'm going to make you perk up.
Pow.
How was your day?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I did.
Wow.
We did it.
I'm hungry.
Yes, sir.
Bon appétit!
Yum.
Mmmm...
Delicious.
Yes, OK.
What the heck!
The cola that Yuka put her body on the line for.
Isn't it so delicious?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
You put your body on the line
We worked all night till about 5:00 in the morning.
Cloth
Cloth.
And when I'm done, it's time for nothingness.
Morning nothingness
I'm exhausted.
Maybe you should just sleep on the couch.
Yeah.
Monadic sofa.
Monadic couch.
That's right.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Have a great day ✍✍.
I'm a little low on tension.
What are we going to do after this?
I want to talk to you.
OK.
Tension up.
Yes, we've succeeded.
Hey, so...
Okay.
Yes, perfect.
Drunk-ish.
Now, that's just right.
I'm turning.
I made a mistake. It's not turning.
Yes, it's OK.
Yes, yes, OK.
Cute.
It's OK.
Yes, yes, OK.
It's good.
He's saying so much.
Yes, OK, that's good.Yes, OK, good, OK.
Now we dance.
Turn slowly.
Cute.
That's great.
Now it's a little more than that.
Look at this! This is amazing!
It's crazy!
There's so many of them!
What do you think?
Sometimes it's dazzling.
It's beautiful. It's like aurora borealis.
It's a pretty light blue. I love blue so much.
I took away Helika's light blue.
Good night.
It's something I shouldn't let go.
I just couldn't help crying
The sky, the blooming flowers, and our story
Let's begin.
Bath! I like having a bathtub.
There is a bathtub. I've never sat in such a pretty bathtub before.
It's pretty slippery.
Bath! I like having a bathtub.
Push it up, push it up.
That one with the round pattern.
Hang it up, the beginning of summer
Thoughts leaping into the sky
Bouncing, bouncing, bouncing
I'll be left behind
Take me with you
Seasonal nightfall
Will you fish?
I'll do it, I'll do it
My heart has turned into a bird
It's a dream, it's a dream, it's a dream
The sky, the fish and us
Let's start falling in love
Mimi.
Yay!
We're good to go.
I was in the lead.
Mimi, you're done.
Thank you very much.
I was last.
You're right.
I was second.
Go home.
I can't go home.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Fish after the rain
My hair is shaking
The wind turns it back into a drop of water
Cover your ears
from the earphones
I've got it.
This sound
Yes, yes, OK.
♪ Cloudy skies by my side ♪
♪ Be in love ♪
- Thank you. Entrance?
- It's finished.
- Thank you very much.
- Yes, sir.
♪ Still the best of the season ♪
♪ Towards pink
♪ Spark Manor
Take care of it. Don't overdo it.
Keep it close.
Unicorn.
Oh, wow.
Oh, it's so cute.
I thought it was a cat.
The fact that it's cute.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I mean, you can win.
Oh, yeah.
I got a room.
The front line.
I remember.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, we're done.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Unicorn. It's over. Unicorn finish.
It was fun.
It's something I've never done before, so I'm looking forward to seeing how it turns out.
I'm looking forward to seeing the finished product.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
Everyone is done.
It's bright outside.
Not yet.
It's going to be a quick and easy day.
It's hard to get into my stomach.
It's going to be a very nice music video.
Please look forward to it.
Enjoy it.
After it's released. Probably.
See you soon.
Shall we all go home together?
While we're annealing.
It's a unicorn finish.
Yes, it was fun. It was fun.
Enjoy.
See you soon.